### 联系方式

www.linkedin.com/in/yuying-ma-aicp-b74987141 (LinkedIn)

#### 热门技能

Aeronautics Aviation planning Grant Writing

### Languages

英语 (Professional Working) 中文 (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications
AICP Certified

# Yuying Ma, AICP

Caltrans HQs - Associate Transportation Planner 美国 加利福尼亚州 洛杉矶

## 个人简介

I am an urban planner with a variety of land use, zoning and platting reviews, data analysis and project management experience. I am proficient in using GIS, Sketchup, Adobe software and Auto CAD. I have very high productivity and am capable of understanding new information at a rapid pace. I believe that long-term planning and comprehensive planning can promote a sense of well-being and resilience of the community while increase the opportunities to lower cost and improve the quality and compatibility of new development.

Yuying's skills include:

- Zoning Experience
- Land Use Planning
- Code Interpretations
- Data Analysis
- Urban Design
- Stakeholder Collaboration
- Customer Service
- Citizen Participation
- Research Analysis
- Site Analysis
- Report Preparation

## 工作经历

Caltrans

7 个月

Associate Transportation Planner 2023 年 10 月 - Present (1 个月)

美国 加利福尼亚州 萨克拉门托

Transportation Planner 2023 年 4 月 - 2023 年 10 月 (7 个月)

美国 加利福尼亚州 洛杉矶

County of Riverside Urban Regional Planner II 2022年11月-2023年4月(6个月)

美国 加利福尼亚州 里弗赛德

Harris County Planner 2021年1月-2022年6月(1年6个月) 10555 Northwest Fwy, Houston, TX 77092

City of San Antonio Planner 2019 年 6 月 - 2021 年 1 月 (1 年 8 个月) 圣安东尼奥,TX,美国

City of Douglasville Planner I 2018年7月-2019年5月(11个月) 6701 Church Street

East Alabama Planning and Development Commission Planning intern 2018年5月-2018年6月(2个月) Anniston, Alabama Area

广西壮族自治区外事侨务办公室 Reception Administration 2015年2月-2015年5月(4个月) 广西 南宁

## 教育经历

Auburn University 硕士, community planning · (2016 - 2018)

广西师范大学 学士, 商务英语·(2011 - 2015)